MEHMET BATUHAN YILMAZ

I graduated from English Architecture in 2019.

I can develop projects with React.js - Vue.js libraries.

Besides HTML5/CSS3, I am proficient in Tailwind and Bootstrap libraries.

I received Manual Testing Expertise and UX/UI Training.

I have knowledge of management and control systems such as Jira, Confluence, Postman, Swagger and Figma, Adobe Graphic Design programs.

- Front-end Developer
- Manual Test Specialist
- UI/UX Designer

I am actively looking for a job in these positions.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

<u>Bab Iot Technologies - Front-end Developer</u> Mayıs 2022 - Ağustos 2022

An interface was designed that the user side of our device, which we developed in the IOT technological revolution, can benefit from, in this process, I took part in Front-end coding, Manual UI Tests and API Tests, UI / UX designs. I worked in the company on a project basis. (Vue.js-React.js-Postman-Swagger-Jira-Confluence- GitHub-Git-Figma-Zeplin-Photohop)

Getasis Bilişim Tek. - Front-end Developer Mart 2022 - Mayıs 2022

Schneider Electric Engineering Front-end development and Manual UI Test and API Testing is the project where I worked as an outsource.

(Vue.js-Postman-Swagger-Thunder-Jira-Confluence-GitHub-Git)

<u>Papirus Digital - Jr. Front-end Developer</u> Ağustos 2021 - Aralık 2021

In the company where I worked as a volunteer intern, I provided visual-design and front-end support.



- mbatuhanylmz@gmail.com
- 05340710261
- 03/11/1996
- İstanbul/Kartal

EDUCATION

• Architecture - English, İstanbul Okan University

'14-'19

• Management Information System - DEF, Anadolu University '20- '24

• Kodluyoruz & Patika.dev

Front-end Developer Education Program

• Udemy - Software Testing House

Software Testing Specialist Training: From Zero to Advanced

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript
- React.js Vue.js Tailwind Bootstrap
- Git GitHub Jira Confluence
- Swagger Postman
- Adobe Photoshop / Illustrator / XD Figma

LANGUAGES

- English(Upper Intermediate B2+)
- German Deutsch (Anfanger A2)

SOCIAL NETWORKS

• GitHub : <u>Link</u>

LinkedIn : <u>Link</u>Portfolio : Link